Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Specifications, correspondence, and other project records, 1891-1985; Series I
  - 22 Medical Center
    - DC-AC Conversion Drawings, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 1170)
    - DC-AC Conversion Construction Drawings, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 1171)
    - Electrical Documentation Submitted for Approval, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 1172)
    - Main Switchgear, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1173)
    - Switchgear Site Distribution, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1174)
    - Electrical Documentation Submitted for Approval, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 1175)
    - Electrical Distribution Equipment, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 1176)
    - Ophthalmology Lab-Operating/ Service Manuals, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 1176.5)
  - 22:25 Brady Memorial Laboratory
    - Renovations, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 1177-1178)
    - Specifications, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1179)
  - 22:46 Private Pavilion
    - Specifications, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 1180)
    - William Wirt Winchester Hospital Laundry Specifications, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 1181)
  - 22:50 Sterling Hall of Medicine
    - Tunnels, 1922-1929 (Box 32, Folder 1182)
    - Lipsky Physical Science Laboratory Shop Drawings, Renovations, 1957-1968 (Box 32, Folder 1183)
    - Medical School Trask Conference, Room Air-Conditioning, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1184)
    - Air-Conditioning Survey, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 1185)
    - Lipsky Physical Science - General Specifications, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 1186)
    - Plumbing and Ventilation Work, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 1187)
    - Addition, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 1188)
    - YPI Gym Stock Issue Room - Specifications and Drawings, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1189)
  - 22:51 Sterling Power Plant
    - Tunnels, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 1190)
    - Miscellaneous Drawings and Documentation, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1191)
    - Electrical Drawings, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1192)
    - Pump House Heating and Ventilation, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1193)
    - Specifications and Contracts, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1194)
    - Miscellaneous Drawings, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1195)
    - Addition Specifications, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 1196)
    - Addition, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 1197)
    - Chilled Water System, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 1198)
    - Chilled Water System, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 1199)
    - Addition, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1200)
  - 22:70 Physical Science Building
    - Purchase Requests, 1967-1969 (Box 32, Folder 1201)
  - 22:162 Edward S. Harkness Hall
    - Hardware Schedule, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 1202)
    - Elevators, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 1203)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 1204)
    - Refrigeration, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 1205)
    - Heating - Forced Hot Water System Equipment/Steam Equipment, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 1206)
  - 22:163 Yale University Cancer Center
    - General Specifications and Miscellaneous, 1982 undated (Box 32, Folder 1207)
  - 23:03 Bethany 40" Telescope Observatory
    - Specifications, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 1208)
    - Renovations, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 1209)
  - 24:02 Outdoor Educational Center
    - Specifications, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 1210)
    - Alterations, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1211)
    - Electrical Work, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1212)
  - 25:01 Baseball Field
    - Miscellaneous Construction Documentation, undated (Box 32, Folder 1213)
  - 25:02 Yale Bowl
    - Press Stand Roof Specifications, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 1214)
    - Toilet Building Specifications, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 1215)
    - Dimension Data for Television, undated (Box 32, Folder 1216)
  - 25:03 Armory
    - Specifications, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 1217-1218)
    - Chronological Statement and Contracts, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 1219)
    - Contracts and Miscellaneous Documentation, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 1220)
  - 25:04 Yale Golf Course
    - Butler Building Specifications, 1963-1965 (Box 33, Folder 1221)
    - Contractual Information and Documentation, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 1222)
    - Reports on Proposals Received on Irrigation and Drawings, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 1223)
  - 25:05 Lapham Field House
    - General and Miscellaneous, 1920 1922-1923 (Box 33, Folder 1224)
    - Plumbing, Heating, Ventilation, 1920-1923 (Box 33, Folder 1225)
  - 25:06 Walter Camp Memorial
    - Masonry Specifications, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 1226)
  - 25:07 Coxe Cage
    - Specifications, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 1227)
    - Roofing Specifications, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 1228)
    - DeWitt Cuyler Field - Renovations, Specifications, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1229)
    - Cullman Tennis Courts Lighting Alterations, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1230)
  - 26:03 Boat House
    - General, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 1231)
  - 26:05 Derby Boat House
    - Alterations, 1958-1964 (Box 33, Folder 1232)
    - Renovations, Specifications, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1233)
    - Specifications for Renovations and Alterations to Yale Boat House Addendum no. 1, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1234)
    - Additions and Alterations, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1235-1236)
    - Specifications, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1237)
  - 27:11 150 Highland St.
    - Renovations, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 1238)
  - 27:12 Bethany Animal Shelter
    - Specifications for Plumbing, Heating, Electrical, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 1239)
    - Specifications - Addendum No. 1, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 1240)
    - Specifications - Addendum No. 2, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 1241)
  - 27:17 Sperry Animal Research Facility
    - Plumbing and Heating, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 1242)
    - Renovations, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1243)
  - 27:18 Haslein Laboratories (270 Crown St.)
    - Miscellaneous Specifications, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 1244)
  - 27:23 Yale Psychiatric Institute
    - Air-Conditioning Installation, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1245)
  - 27:36 Norfolk Music Camp
    - Kitchen Renovations, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 1246)
  - 27:37 Yale Press Book Warehouse
    - Miscellaneous Documentation, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 1247)
  - Smith, Cyril K., Jr., Architect
    - Specifications for Barracks Facilities for Troop E Area, State Police Department Project BI-N-90, undated (Box 34, Folder 1248)
  - Gruen Associates
    - Outline Specifications for Three Level Parking Facility and Adjacent Surface Parking Lot for Yale University, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1249)
  - Miscellaneous Buildings
    - Soccer/Lacrosse Stadium, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1250)
    - Police Department - Mobile Relay Station, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1251)
    - Long Wharf, Bake Shop Relocation, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1252)
    - Naval Equipment - NROTC, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 1253)
    - Vande Graff Building Mechanical Specifications, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 1254)
    - Animal House Specifications, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 1255)
    - Botanical Gardens Fountain Picture, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1256)
    - Greenwich House #3, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 1257)
    - 38 Whitney Ave. - Alterations, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1258)
    - 179 Linden St. - Renovations, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 1259)
    - 493 College St. - Air-Conditioning (Box 34, Folder 1260)
    - Installation, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1260)
    - St. Margaret's School, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 1261)
    - Sears, Roebuck, Inc. - Bridgeport, CT - Proposed Third Floor, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 1262)
  - Electrical Documentation
    - Details: Electric Fixtures, Miscellaneous Typical Heating Details, 1931-1934 1942 (Box 34, Folder 1263)
    - The Hinchman Company: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1264)
    - Electrical Testing, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 1265)
    - Yale University Plans and Specifications - Electrical, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 1266)
  - Cathodic Protection
    - The Hinchman Company
      - Correspondence Concerning Cathodic Protection Inspection, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1267)
      - Annual Inspection of Cathodic Protection Systems, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1268)
      - Cathodic Protection Inspection, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 1269)
      - Cathodic Protection Inspection, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1270)
      - Cathodic Protection Inspection, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1271)
  - Lighting
    - Electrical Light Controls, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 1272)
    - Ultraviolet Lights, 1964, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 1273)
    - Undergraduate Housing Lighting Review, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1274)
    - Energy Conservation Lighting Installation, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1275)
  - Conversion to Alternating Current
    - Diagrams and Graphs, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1276)
    - Diagrams and Summaries, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1277)
    - Diagrams, Photographs, Summaries, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1278)
    - Tests and Readings, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1279)
    - Specifications, Installation, Instructions, Diagrams, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1280)
    - Load Test Data, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1281)
    - Central Power Plant: Diagrams, Summary, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 1282)
    - Electrical Distribution System, undated (Box 34, Folder 1283)
  - Mechanical
    - Water Heater Guarantee and Instructions, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 1284)
    - Olive Mechanical Contractors, Inc.: Information on Pumps, Unit Heaters, Temperature Controls, Heat Transfer Package and Humidifiers, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1285)
    - Installation of New Oil Burners, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1286)
  - Tunnels
    - Wall St., 1912 (Box 34, Folder 1287)
    - Steam Piping, 1917-1930 (Box 34, Folder 1288)
    - Specifications, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 1289)
    - Specifications, 1929-1931 (Box 35, Folder 1290)
    - Sheffield Scientific School, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 1291)
    - Masonry, undated (Box 35, Folder 1292)
  - Ventilation
    - Air-Conditioning: Brochures, Specifications, 1958-1964 (Box 35, Folder 1293)
    - Air Filters - Brochures, Specifications, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1294)
    - Central University Area: Air-Conditioning and Filter Survey, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1295)
    - Division of Utilities and Engineering Services: Survey Work for Temperature Control, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1296)
  - Pipes
    - The Hinchman Company: Instructions, Specifications, Bill, Suggested Suppliers, and Drawings, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1297)
    - Report of Corrosion Survey, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1298)
    - Division 15 Work To Be Done: Pipe Insulation, Plumbing, Air-Ducts, Sprinklers, undated (Box 35, Folder 1299)
  - Insulation and Storm Windows
    - Status Sheets and Drawings, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 1300)
  - Building Assignment Plans
    - Various Floor Plans, 1967-1973 (Box 35, Folder 1301)
  - Building Alterations
    - Planning Committee on Coeducation Housing, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1302)
    - Handicapped Access, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1303)
- Drawings, 1912-1988; Series II
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  This series contains architectural drawings removed from files in Series I for storage and preservation reasons.
  Building construction, renovation, and maintenance plans from 1912 to 1988 comprise this set of architectural drawings, which range in content from general assignment floor plans to detailed sketches of electrical fixtures and equipment wiring. These drawings have served as important working documents to architects involved in the details of restoration, alteration, and additional building.
  - 1:02 Connecticut Hall
    - Restorations, 1952-1953 (Box 36)
    - Library: Proposed Stair Alterations, 1970 (Box 36)
    - Assignment Plans, 1975 (Box 36)
  - 1:17 Dwight Hall
    - Lighting: Organ Console, Seating, 1931 (Box 37)
    - Organ Installation, 1970 (Box 37)
    - Organ, 1972 (Box 37)
    - Electrical Mechanical, 1974 (Box 37)
  - 1:20 Street Hall
    - Ventilation, 1963-1964 (Box 38)
    - Alterations and Mechanical, 1963 (Box 38)
  - 1 Old Campus
    - Miscellaneous Plans of Old Campus (Box 39)
    - Lighting Plans, 1965, 1969, undated (Box 39)
  - 1:23 Farnam Hall
    - pump wiring, 1976 (Box 193)
  - 1:24 Durfee Hall
    - Wiring for pump, 1955 (Box 193)
    - Mechanical and electrical room plan, undated (Box 193)
    - Assignment plans, 1960-1977 (Box 193)
    - Renovations, 1977 (Box 193)
    - Electrical and construction plans, 1972 (Box 193)
  - 1:25 Battell Chapel
    - Alms box, 1927 (Box 193)
  - 1:29 Lawrence Hall
    - Lighting equipment and wiring, 1964, 1976 (Box 193)
  - 1:32 Welch Hall
    - First Floor: Interior Doors, 1938 (Box 41)
    - Alterations to Campus Police Basement, 1962 (Box 41)
    - Lighting Equipment, 1964 (Box 41)
    - Shower door, 1939 (Box 193)
  - 1:33 Vanderbilt Hall
    - Mechanical: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 41)
    - Typical Air Compressor, 1976 (Box 42)
  - 1:35 Phelps Hall
    - Library Furniture, 1964 (Box 43)
    - Architectural Details, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Elevators, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Various Alterations, 1966 (Box 43)
    - Cabinets, Dispatchers, 1975 (Box 43)
  - 1:39 Linsly-Chittenden Hall
    - Mechanical, 1928 (Box 44)
    - Chase Metalworks, 1929 (Box 44)
    - Skylights, 1930 (Box 44)
    - Skylight: Proposed Changes, 1931 (Box 44)
    - Toilet Room Alteration, 1973 (Box 44)
  - 1:40 Wright Hall
    - Elevator, 1931 (Box 45)
    - Mechanical, 1937 (Box 45)
    - Pump Control Circuits, 1963 (Box 45)
    - Color Schemes, 1968 (Box 45)
    - Basement Floor Alterations, 1975 (Box 45)
  - 1:43 McClellan Hall
    - Woodwork: Mantels, 1925 (Box 45)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall
    - Steel Cabinets, Panel-Board, 1924 (Box 46)
    - Panel-Board, 1925 (Box 46)
    - Window Schedules, Panel-Boards, 1926 (Box 46)
    - Tank, Schedules of Lighting Fixtures, 1927 (Box 46)
    - Steel Framing: Ninth Floor and Roof, 1930 (Box 46)
    - Electrical: Distribution Equipment, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Elevator, 1976 (Box 46)
    - Renovations of Chaplain"s Basement and Rooms, 1977 (Box 46)
  - 2:11 305 Crown St.
    - Floor Plans, 1968-1969 (Box 47)
  - 2:15 Yale University Press (149 York St.)
    - Working Drawings: General Baking Co., 1924-1925 (Box 48)
    - Electrical, 1959 (Box 48)
    - Equipment Layout, 1959 (Box 48)
    - Cabinets and Shelving, 1959 (Box 48)
    - Landscaping, 1959 (Box 48)
    - Acoustical Insulation, 1959-1961 (Box 48)
    - Structural, 1959, undated (Box 48)
    - Assignment Plans, 1960 (Box 48)
    - Second Floor Alteration, 1962 (Box 48)
    - Preliminary Drawings, undated (Box 48)
  - 2:19 1104 Chapel
    - Temporary Office for Fire Marshall - Floor Plan and Partition Elevation, 1970 (Box 49)
  - 2:29 Yale Repertory Theatre
    - Basement Plan, 1969 (Box 50)
    - Seats, 1971-1973 (Box 50)
    - Elevator, 1973, undated (Box 50)
    - Stage, 1974 (Box 50)
    - Seating Plan, 1974-1975 (Box 50)
    - Deluge System, 1975 (Box 50)
    - Sprinkler Layouts, 1975 (Box 50)
    - Patch Panel, 1975-1976 (Box 50)
    - Electrical, 1976 (Box 50)
    - Mechanical, 1976 (Box 50)
  - 2:33 British Art Center
    - General Construction, 1973-1974 (Box 51)
    - General Construction, 1975-1976 (Box 51)
    - Atticus Floor Plan, 1979 (Box 51)
  - 3:07 School of Drama/University Theatre
    - Mechanical/Plumbing, 1926 (Box 52)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1954 (Box 52)
    - Mechanical, 1957 (Box 52)
    - Structural, 1957 (Box 52)
    - Floor Plans, 1971 (Box 52)
    - Main Stage and Console, 1974 (Box 52)
    - Mechanical, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 3:25 Davenport and Pierson Colleges
    - Electrical, 1930-1932 (Box 53)
    - Elevators, 1930-1932 (Box 53)
    - General Construction, 1930-1932 (Box 53)
    - Kitchen Equipment and Construction, 1930-1932 (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1966 (Box 54)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1967 (Box 54)
    - Dining Hall Alterations, 1972 (Box 54)
    - Student Housing Renovations, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 54)
  - 3:32 204 York St.
    - Service Bar, undated (Box 55)
    - Snack Bar Alterations, 1973 (Box 55)
  - 3:37 217 Park St.
    - Fire Escape, 1960 (Box 56)
    - Architectural, Mechanical, Electrical, 1984 (Box 56)
  - 3:43 Art and Architecture Building
    - General Construction, 1948-1950 (Box 57)
    - General Construction, 1962-1965 (Box 57)
    - Renovations, 1973 (Box 57)
    - Library: Architectural and Electrical, 1974 (Box 57)
    - General Construction, 1980 (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 57)
  - 3:57 264 York St.
    - Renovations, 1983 (Box 58)
  - 4:18 149 Elm St. (Faculty Club)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1963 (Box 59)
    - Plot Plans, 1963 (Box 59)
    - Proposed Alterations, 1963 (Box 59)
  - 4:22 232 York St.
    - Fire Escape, 1975 (Box 59)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle (Harkness Tower)/Branford and Saybrook Colleges
    - Copies of Original Plans, 1919 (Box 60)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1927-1932 (Box 60)
    - Piping, 1930-1934 (Box 60)
    - Dumbwaiter, 1931-1933 (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous Mechanical Specifications, 1932-1933 (Box 60)
    - Elevators, 1932 (Box 60)
    - Heating and Ventilating Apparatus, 1932 (Box 60)
    - Wiring Diagrams, 1932 (Box 60)
    - Grille Work, 1933 (Box 60)
    - Lighting Fixtures, 1933 (Box 60)
    - Refrigeration, 1933 (Box 60)
    - Furnishings, 1933 (Box 60)
    - Louvers, 1933 (Box 60)
    - Proposed Partitions, 1962 (Box 60)
    - Basement Renovations, 1969 (Box 60)
    - Kitchen Renovations, 1972 (Box 60)
    - Branford College Renovations, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Saybrook College Lighting, undated (Box 60)
  - 4:34 Jonathan Edwards College
    - Electrical, 1931 (Box 61)
    - Elevators, 1931-1932 (Box 61)
    - Furniture Arrangements, 1931-1932 (Box 61)
    - General Construction, 1931-1932 (Box 61)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1931-1932 (Box 61)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1931-1932 (Box 61)
    - Mechanical, 1953 (Box 61)
    - Elevator, 1957 (Box 61)
    - Elevator, 1965-1967 (Box 61)
    - Weir Hall: Floor Plans, 1970 (Box 61)
  - 4:37 Art Gallery
    - Electrical Work, 1926 (Box 62)
    - Louvers, 1926 (Box 62)
    - Elevators, 1927 (Box 62)
    - Special Electrical Panels, 1927 (Box 62)
    - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 62)
    - Third Floor Electrical Works, 1928, 1974 (Box 62)
    - Proposed Stairway, 1930 (Box 62)
    - Additional Rooms, 1930 (Box 62)
    - Iron and Grille Work, 1944 (Box 62)
    - Fan Assembly, 1946 (Box 62)
    - Floor Plan, 1949 (Box 62)
    - Fire Alarm System, 1952 (Box 62)
    - Skylight, 1953 (Box 62)
    - Second Floor Temperature Control, 1959 (Box 62)
    - Basement Alterations, 1964 (Box 62)
    - Electrical Works, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Basement Renovations, 1976 (Box 62)
    - Electrical Wiring, 1976 (Box 62)
  - 5:10 Hall of Graduate Studies
    - Assembly of Ice Machine, 1929 (Box 63)
    - Details of Elevator Shaft, Trench and Pit, Sidewalk Elevator, 1930 (Box 63)
    - Elevators, 1931 (Box 63)
    - Kitchen Equipment and Fixtures, 1931 (Box 63)
    - Electrical and Lighting, 1931 (Box 63)
    - Heating, Radiators, Ventilation, 1931 (Box 64)
    - Duct-Work, Tunnel, Automatic Starting Speed Regulator, 1931 (Box 64)
    - Electrical, Lighting, 1932 (Box 64)
    - Heating Valve Layout, 1932 (Box 64)
    - Elevator Control, 1932 (Box 64)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1932 (Box 64)
    - Lighting Fixtures, Lamp Shade, 1932 (Box 64)
    - Furniture, Shelving, 1932 (Box 64)
    - Bookcase, 1938 (Box 64)
    - Ventilation Wiring Diagrams, 1958 (Box 64)
    - Air-Condition System, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Proposed Air-Conditioning System, 1964 (Box 64)
    - Wiring for Dining Hall, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Fire Alarm System, 1972 (Box 64)
    - Ventilation, 1981 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 64)
  - 5:16 Morse College
    - Elevators, 1961 (Box 65)
    - Fire Alarm, 1961 (Box 65)
    - Courtyard Gate, Master's House, 1962 (Box 65)
    - Renovations, 1974 (Box 65)
  - 5:17 Ezra Stiles College
    - Loading Dock, Basement Plans, 1960 (Box 65)
    - Fire Alarm System, 1961 (Box 65)
    - Passenger Elevator, Stiles Tower, 1961 (Box 65)
    - Basement and First Floor Renovations, 1976 (Box 65)
  - 5:16, 5:17 Morse and Ezra Stiles Colleges
    - Fire Alarm System, 1960-1965 (Box 65)
    - Piping, Ventilation, 1960 (Box 65)
    - Mechanicals, 1960 (Box 65)
    - Electrical and Lighting, 1960 (Box 65)
    - Dining Hall Alterations, 1972 (Box 65)
    - Flagstone Restoration, 1972 (Box 65)
    - Assignment Plans, undated (Box 65)
    - Architectural Details, 1960 (Box 66)
    - Site Plan, 1960 (Box 66)
    - Cabinets and Furniture, Kitchen Equipment, 1961 (Box 68)
    - Electrical, Mechanical, Lighting, 1961 (Box 68)
    - Ventilation, 1961 (Box 68)
    - Elevators, 1961 (Box 68)
    - Architectural Details, General Plans, 1961 (Box 69)
    - Ventilation, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Shelving, Cabinetry, Fixtures, Kitchen Equipment, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Electrical, Mechanical, Lighting, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Architectural Details, 1962 (Box 70)
    - Details of Gates, Master"s Mailboxes, 1962-1963 (Box 70)
    - Supplementary Electric Heating, Buildings E-6, E-4, W-1, Receptacle Panels, 1963 (Box 70)
  - 5:18 Yale Co-op
    - Architectural Details, 1961 (Box 71)
    - Electrical, Mechanical, 1961 (Box 71)
    - Electrical, Mechanical, Refrigeration and Fan System Control, 1962 (Box 71)
    - Elevators and Dumbwaiter, 1962 (Box 71)
    - Architectural Details, 1962 (Box 71)
  - 6:04 Central Power Plant
    - Chilled Water System, 1967-1968 (Box 72)
    - Space Heater, 1963 (Box 72)
    - Electric, 1955-1957 (Box 73)
  - 6:05 20 Ashmun St.
    - Alterations, 1964 (Box 74)
    - Heating/Air Conditioning, 1964 (Box 74)
    - Air Conditioning Layout, 1968 (Box 74)
    - Third Floor Alterations, 1968 (Box 74)
    - Third Floor Assignment Plans, 1970 (Box 74)
  - 6:16 Payne Whitney Gymnasium
    - Electrical Fixtures, 1930-1931 (Box 75)
    - Elevators, 1930 (Box 75)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1931-1933 (Box 76)
    - Exit Signs, 1931-1934 (Box 76)
    - Rowing Tanks, 1934 (Box 76)
    - Electrical, 1930-1932 (Box 77)
    - General Construction, 1930-1932 (Box 78)
    - General Construction, 1971-1975 (Box 78)
  - 6:17 Ray Tompkins House
    - Bowling Alley, 1931 (Box 79)
    - Electrical, 1931-1932 (Box 79)
    - Heating, 1931-1932 (Box 79)
    - Kitchen Equipment and Various Details, 1931-1932 (Box 79)
    - Lighting Equipment, 1931-1932 (Box 79)
    - Dormitories, 1932 (Box 79)
    - Schedule of Doors, 1932 (Box 79)
    - Architectural, Electrical, 1968 (Box 79)
  - 6:27 26/28 Ashmun St.
    - Alterations, 1975 (Box 80)
  - 6:28 50 Ashmun St.
    - Office Alterations, 1964 (Box 80)
  - 7:31 Sterling Memorial Library
    - Plumbing, 1927 (Box 81)
    - Ventilation, 1928 (Box 81)
    - Fan Design (Ventilation), 1928 (Box 81)
    - Grille Work - Radiators, 1929 (Box 81)
    - Elevators, 1929 (Box 81)
    - Switchboards, 1929 (Box 81)
    - Book and Map Case, 1930 (Box 81)
    - Exhibit Cases, 1930 (Box 81)
    - Book Conveyer, 1930 (Box 82)
    - Cabinets, 1930 (Box 82)
    - Electrical Panels, 1930 (Box 82)
    - Electrical Wiring - Dumbwaiter, 1930 (Box 82)
    - Miscellaneous Electrical and Mechanical Drawings, 1930 (Box 82)
    - Proposed Film Storage Vault, 1933 (Box 82)
    - Third Floor Ventilation and Exhaust, 1940 (Box 82)
    - Window Designs, undated (Box 82)
    - Pneumatic Tube System, 1962 (Box 83)
    - Reciprocating Lift, 1962 (Box 83)
    - Miscellaneous Mechanical Drawings, 1962-1963 (Box 83)
    - Cubicles, 1966 (Box 83)
    - Book Stacks, 1969 (Box 83)
    - Annex - Job Schedule, 1969 (Box 83)
    - Stairwell Designs, 1969 (Box 83)
    - Electrical Work, 1969-1970 (Box 83)
    - Lighting Recommendations - Nave, 1970 (Box 83)
    - Document Room - Alterations, 1972 (Box 83)
    - Book Display Cases, 1973 (Box 83)
    - Alterations, 1974-1975 (Box 83)
  - 7:36 Trumbull College
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1928-1932 (Box 84)
    - Piping, 1930 (Box 84)
    - Basement Plumbing Plans, 1931 (Box 84)
    - Lighting Equipment, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Miscellaneous Electrical and Mechanical Specifications, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Heating, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Heating and Ventilating Apparatus, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Schedule of Doors, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Electrical Panels, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Steel Partitions, 1932 (Box 84)
    - Elevators, 1932-1933 (Box 84)
    - Grille Work, 1933 (Box 85)
    - Dining Hall, 1933 (Box 85)
    - Miscellaneous Floor Plans, undated (Box 85)
    - Dining Hall Main Ceiling, 1933 (Box 85)